ryrob.com 2019-12-29

# Privacy Policy | RyRob.com: A Blog by Ryan Robinson | Learn How to Blog and Make Money on the Internet

### This privacy policy sets out how **  Ryan Robinson** ** ** uses and protects any information that you volunteer when you use this website.

 _Last Updated: November 5, 2018_

We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

We can be reached via e-mail at ryan@ryrob.com

Mailing Address:

 _Ryan Robinson  | 1378 McAllister St, #3 | San Francisco, CA 94115_

This Privacy Policy explains how information about you is collected, used and disclosed by Ryan Robinson (“Company,” “we,” “us” or “our”). This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect when you use our websites, mobile applications and the services, content and materials made available through our websites or mobile applications (collectively, the “Services”), or when you otherwise interact with us.

 **The Important Stuff:  **We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your explicit permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting _if_ you tell us that you wish this to happen.

 **More Important Stuff:** If you believe that any information we are holding about you is incorrect, incomplete or wish for it to be deleted, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address or email address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect or remove any information you request to be deleted.

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the “Last Updated” date at the top of this policy and, in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as by adding a statement to our website or by sending you a notification). We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy whenever you access the Services or otherwise interact with us to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

## Collection of Information

###  **Information You Provide to Us**

We collect information you provide directly to us. For example, we collect information when you create an account, participate in any interactive features of the Services, subscribe to a newsletter or email list, participate in an event, survey, contest or promotion, make a purchase, communicate with us via third-party social media sites, request customer support or otherwise communicate with us.

The types of information we may collect include your:

  * Name
  * Email address
  * Password
  * Postal address
  * Phone number
  * Occupation
  * Employer information
  * Photo
  * Securely stored payment information (such as your credit or debit card and billing address)
  * Preference or interest data
  * Any other information you choose to provide.

###  **Information We Collect Automatically**

When you access or use our Services, we automatically collect information about you, including:

 **Log Information:** We collect log information about your use of the Services, including your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, web request, access times, pages viewed, web browser, links clicked and the page you visited before navigating to the Services.

 **Mobile Device Information:** We collect information about the mobile device you use to access our Services, including the hardware model, operating system and version, unique device identifiers, mobile network information and information about your use of our mobile applications.

 **Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies:** We and our service providers use various technologies to collect information, including cookies and web beacons. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory that help us improve our Services and your experience, see which areas and features of our Services are popular, and count visits. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in our Services or emails and help deliver cookies, count visits, and understand usage and campaign effectiveness. For more information about cookies, and how to disable them, please see “Your Choices” below.

###  **Information We Collect From Other Sources**

We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect through our Services. For example, if you create or log into your account through a third-party social media site, we will have access to certain information from that site, such as your name, account information and friends lists, in accordance with the authorization procedures determined by such social media site; we may also collect information about you when you post content to our pages/feeds on third-party social media sites.

##  **Use of Information**

We may use information about you for various purposes, including to:

  * Provide, maintain, improve and promote our products and services;
  * Provide and deliver the information, products and services you request, process transactions and send you related information, including confirmations and receipts;
  * Send you technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;
  * Respond to your comments, questions and requests, and provide customer service;
  * Communicate with you about products, services, surveys, offers, promotions, rewards and events offered by
  * Company and others, and provide news and information we think will be of interest to you;
  * Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our Services;
  * Personalize and improve the Services and provide advertisements, content or features that match user profiles or interests;
  * Facilitate contests, sweepstakes and promotions, and process and deliver entries and rewards;
  * Link or combine with information we get from others to help understand your needs and provide you with better service; and
  * Carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected.

We are based in the United States and the information we collect is governed by U.S. law. By accessing or using the Services or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing and transfer of information in and to the U.S. and other countries.

##  **Sharing of Information**

We may share information about you as follows or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy:

  * With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work or perform services on our behalf;
  * When you participate in the interactive areas of our Services, certain information you provide may be displayed to other users, such as your name, photo, comments and other information you choose to provide;
  * In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law, regulation or legal process;
  * If we believe your actions are inconsistent with our user agreements or policies, or to protect the rights, property and safety of Company or others;
  * In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company; and
  * With your consent or at your direction.

##  **Social Sharing Features**

The Services may offer social sharing features and other integrated tools (such as the Facebook “Like” button), which let you share actions you take on our Services with other media, and vice versa. Your use of such features enables the sharing of information with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the entity that provides the social sharing feature. For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and processing in connection with social sharing features, please visit the privacy policies of the entities that provide these features.

##  **Advertising and Analytics Services Provided by Others**

We may allow others to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet and to provide analytics services. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Services and other websites, including your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked and conversion information. This information may be used by Company and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our Services and other websites and better understand your online activity. For more information about interest-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for behavioral advertising purposes by companies that participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance, please visit www.aboutads.info/choices.

##  **Affiliate Disclosure**

Ryan Robinson is an affiliate of many online tools, services, and products. Links on the Site may be affiliate links and Ryan Robinson may earn commissions for purchases that are made by visitors to the Site.

##  **Security**

Company takes reasonable measures to help protect information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

##  **Your Choices**

###  **Account Information**

You may review, correct or modify information maintained in your online account at any time by logging into your account and updating your profile information or by emailing us at ryan@ryrob.com. If you wish to delete or deactivate your account, please email us at ryan@ryrob.com, but note that some information you provide through the Services may continue to be accessible (e.g., comments you submit through the Services) and that we may continue to store information about you as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may also retain cached or archived copies of information about you for a certain period of time.

###  **Cookies**

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability or functionality of our Services

###  **Promotional Communications**

You may opt out of receiving promotional communications from us by following the instructions in those communications or by sending an email to ryan@ryrob.com. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional communications, such as those about your account or our ongoing business relations.

##  **Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at ryan@ryrob.com

##  **Refund Policy**

To be eligible for a refund, you must make a refund request through our customer service team (ryan@ryrob.com) within the applicable time period for your program as set forth below.

Your online access to all program materials is contingent on maintaining good standing in all of our programs for which you have registered. A failure to pay an installment for any program may result in the suspension or termination of your account and access to programs.

Our standard refund policy is a 60-Day, 100% Money-Back Guarantee.

If you don’t love one of our programs, just email ryan@ryrob.com at ANY TIME during the first 60 days and show us you’re doing the exercises and not getting results. We’ll refund 100% of the purchase price.
